ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4014
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- B-1-2: Maintenance and Repair. 1965-1975. (Box 17)
  - B-1-2 Maintenance and Repair, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - B-2 Office Space, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - B-2 Office Space, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - B-3-2 - Building Plans, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - B-3-3 Building Equipment, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - B-4 -- Ives Hall Room Use, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - B-5 NYC Apartment, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - B-6 1969 Space Study for N.Y.S. Audit and Control (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - B-7 IBEW Building, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Leg. 1 -- Legislation (Federal), 1965 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Leg-1-d Higher Education Act of 1965 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Leg-1-h International Education Act, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Leg-2 Fair Labor Standards, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Leg-4 Taylor Act, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Leg-5 Legislation, Misc., 1968-1970 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- M-1: Coordinator of Special Programs. 1966-1975. (Box 18)
  - M-1 Coordinator of Special Programs 1969- (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - M-2 - Pol. And Procedures (Charges, Conf. proceedings, employment of staff), 1973 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - M-3 Reports, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - M-4 - Correspondence rel. Programs, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - M-4-1 - Conference Program, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - M-4-2 Construction Programs, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - M-4-4 Labor-Management Programs, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - M-4-3 Railroad Programs, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - M-4-5 Affirmative Action Conference - 1976 (Dyer-DOL) (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - M-15 Weinberg Seminar, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - M-4-6 R. Dennis Public Sector Conference (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - M-4-7 Labor-Mgmt. Conf., NYC etc. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - M-30 -- Non-School Sponsored Programs (On-Campus), 1977 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - M-31 -- Non-School Sponsored Programs (Off-Campus), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - M-32 Ithaca Center for the Arts, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - PR-3 International Labor Training Prog. (Completed 1963) (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - PR-14 Salary Survey Perrins, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - PR-25 Public Service Training Program (Donovan), 1967 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - PR-28 ASPA Accreditation Committee, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - PR-29 Skill Advancement (NYC), 1971 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - PR-32 Ford Foundation, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - PR-33 Ford Found "Women's Participation in Labor Union Leadership, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - PR-35 -- NSF - Peru Project - Whyte, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - PR-36 Salary Surveys, 1968-1970 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - PR-37 Community Action Skills Development, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - PR-38 Rehabilitation Poverty Project (HEW), 1970 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - PR-39 OEO Project - Huttar, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- PR(cont)-39: OEO Project (Huttar) (Dennis). 1969-1975. (Box 19)
  - PR-40 Middle Management, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - PR-42 Regional Study, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - PR-43 Consortium on Community Crises, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - PR-44 Rural Manpower Project, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - PR-45 Gordon Projects, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - PR-46 Farm Labor Proj., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - PR-47 Action Project, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - PR-50 NSK - Longtdnl. Study of Bureaucracies (Meyer), 1972 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - PR-51 - Ford Foundation Grant (Yaffe), 1974 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - PR-52 NIH Conference (Hutter), 1972 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - PR-53 GOOGIE (Cicione), 1973 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - PR-54 Quality of Work, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - PR-54 Quality of Work Project - Documents, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - PR-56 Bayberry Project, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - PR-58 Trade Union Health Education Project, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - PR-61 Effectiveness of U-M Plant Safety, etc. (Kochan), 1974 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - PU-1 Publications - General, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - PU-1-2 Publication Plans Cost and Expenditures (68-1971), 1968-1971 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - PU-1-2 Publication Plans Cost and Expenditures (1972- (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - PU-3 Publications- Procedure and Policy, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - PU-4 ILR Review, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - PU-5-2 ILR Research Report, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - PU-6 Special Mailing List (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - PU-7 Technical Reports Series, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - PU-9 Publications Assn. in Industrial Relations (PAIR), 1971 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - PU-10 Issues in Industrial Society, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - PU-11 ILR School Announcement Revision, 1973-1975 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - PU-13 Misc. ILR Publications, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- R-1a: Research Policy. 1969-1975. (Box 20)
  - R-1 General, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - R-1a Research Policy, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - R-1-1 Research Associates, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - R-1-2 -- Procedures for Preparing Research Proposals, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - R-1-3 -- Research Proposals (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - R-1-3a Correspondence rel, Research Proposals, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - R-1-4 -- Institutional Research, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - R-1-5 Census of Research Projects (1966- (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - R-3-1 - Haifa University, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - R-3-11 -- Western Europe (Turin, Italy), 1973 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - R-4 Sass (Gordon/McGinnis), 1974 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - R-5-2 -- Research IIRA (Intern. Ind. Rel. Assn.), 1971 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - R-6 Survey Center, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - R-6 Survey Research Center, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - R-7 Computer Activities Group, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- ST-1: Program & Policy (could include:. 1969-1975. (Box 21)
  - ST-1 Program and Policy, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - ST-0 Student Data, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - ST-1a Orientation Program (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - ST-1b Students Weekend and Parents Weekend, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - ST-1c Senior Banquet (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - ST-1-1 Undergraduate Curriculum, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - ST-1d Class Receptions (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - ST-1-1a - Curriculum of other Cornell Schools or College, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - ST-1-2 Instructional Computing, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - ST-1-4 Extension Program for Undergraduates, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - ST-1-5 Undergraduate Field Study Support, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - ST-1-6 Overseas Study Program, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - St-1-7 Junior Semester in New York City, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - ST-1-8 Restrictions Out-of-Colleges Electives, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - ST-2 ILR Student Council, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - ST-3-7, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - ST-2-1 Transfer Organization and Students (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - ST-2-2 Student Course Evaluation, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - ST-2-3 Student Faculty Seminar Com., 1973 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - ST-3 Daniel Alpern Scholarship, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - ST-3-1 Borden Company Scholarship, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - ST-3-2 Sidney Hillman Scholarship, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - ST-3-4 Kennecott Copper, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - ST-3-5 NYS Council of Machinists Award, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - ST-3-6 Local 325 Scholarship, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - ST-3-8 University Scholarship, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - ST-3-9 Mortimer Horowitz Freshman Scholarship, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - ST-3-11 James Campbell Memorial Fund (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - ST-3-12 Irving M. Ives Awards (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - ST-3-13 Clem Miller Scholarship (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - ST-3-14 Olin Summer Project Grant Program, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - ST-3-15 Sen. Kennedy Internship Program, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - ST-3-16 Eleanor Emerson Internship, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - ST-3-17 ILO Summer Internship, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - ST-3-18 ILR Scholarship Fund, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - ST-3-20 Scholarship (General), 1975 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - ST-3-22 Saul Wallen Internship in Community Dispute (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - ST-3-23 Eric Polisar Memorial Fund, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - ST-3-24 - State Senate Labor Comm. Dispute Settlement, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - ST-5 Undergraduates General -- Current, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - ST-6 Undergraduate Teaching Assistants, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - ST-7 Student Publications, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - ST-7-1ILR Forum, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - ST-8 Student Support Services (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - ST-9 Min. Stu. Orgs., etc. (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - ST-10 Admissions ILR, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - ST-11 Tuition and Fees, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 47)
- ST-19: Graduate Recruiting. 1968-1975. (Box 22)
  - ST-19 -- Graduate Recruiting, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - ST-20 - Program and Policy, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - ST-20a Orientation Program (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - ST-20b Graduate Student Association (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - ST-21 Graduate Field, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - ST-21a - MILR Degree, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - ST-21b Graduate Research Support and Thesis, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - ST-22 Grad. School Notices to Field Reps., 1974 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - ST-23 - Assistantships (Current) (Prior data sent to ORI), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - ST-23a - Policy Statements rel. Graduate Assistants, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - ST-24 - ILR Fellowship Fund, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - ST-24a - National Defense Education Act Fellowship Prog., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - St-24c -- Kennecott Copper Fellowship, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - ST-24z - Fellowships and Scholarships (Gen.), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - ST-24e Alcoa Fdn. Graduate Fellowship, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - St-25 - Grad. Students (General), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - ST-26 Foreign Graduate Students, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - ST-32 Corporate Alumni Advisory Group, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - ST-30-1 Alumni Secretary and Counselor, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - ST-33-2 Faculty Advisory Committee to Alumni, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - ST-33- ILR Alumni Assoc., 1972 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - ST-30 ILR Alumni 1966 Forward (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - ST-33-1 Alumni Assoc. Advisory Board, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - ST-34 Judge William B. Groat Jr. Alumni Award, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- ST-3: Daniel Alpern Scholarship. 1968-1975. (Box 23)
  - ST-39 Department Chairmen, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - ST-39-1 Department Seminars, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - ST-40 Schedules and Program Planning, 1969-1971 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - ST-40-1 Adjunct Professors, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - ST-40-2 Visiting Professors, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - ST-41a Job Applicants - General, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - ST-42 Organizational Behavior, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - ST-43 Collective Bargaining, Labor Law, etc., 1975 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - ST-44 Labor Economics and Income Security, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - ST-45 International and Comparative Labor Relations, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - ST-45a Job Applicants International and Comp. Labor Rel., 1975 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - ST-47 Manpower Studies, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - ST-48 ILR-Cornell Credit Courses -- N.Y.C., 1975 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - ST-49 ILR Catalog, 1965-1974 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - ST-50 Summer Session and Extramural, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - ST-51 NYC Credit and Certificate Prog., 1975 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - ST-51-1 NYC Credit Prog. Course Offerings and Handbook, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- ST-51: Two-year Assoc. Degree Program. 1971-1975. (Box 24)
  - ST-51 ILR Credit and Certificate Program NYC, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - ST-51 Credit and Certificate Program 4-12/73, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - ST-51 Two Year Associate Degree, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - ST-51 ILR Credit and Certificate Program 11-12/72, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - ST-51 Two Year Associate Degree Program, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - ILR Credit and Certificate Program 11-12/72, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - ST-51 ILR Credit and Certificate Program 5-10/72, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - ST-51 Two Year Assoc. Degree Program 1/72 - 4/72, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - ST-51 Two-Year Assoc. Degree Program, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - ST-52 ILR Summer Institute, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - ST-53 ILR Expansion N.Y.C., 1974 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - ST-54 Extension Department (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - ST-55 Field Studies Coord., 1977 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- A-4-6: Council of Presidents. 1971-1975. (Box 25)
  - SUNY Council of Presidents 1973-74, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - A-4-6 - S.U. Council of Pres., 1973 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - A-4-6 - S.U. Council of Pres. (71 thru 72), 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - A-4-6 - S.U. Council of Pres. (70-71), 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - A-4-6 S.U. Council of Presidents, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - A-6-9a Planning Committee (Expanded) (Provost's Comm. 10/70-8/71), 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - A-6-20 -- Ad Hoc Com. (Recorded), 1971 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - State of University of New York, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    Scope and Contents
    Bound
  - Council of Presidents, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- A-6-20: Ad Hoc Committees (cont.). 1969-1975. (Box 26)
  - A-6-1a Extension Committee on International Activision, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - A-6-15 International Activities Committee, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - A-6-17 Summer Session Committee, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - A-6-20 Completed Ad Hoc Committees, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - A-6-20 - Ad Hoc Committee In-Service Masters Completed, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - A-6-20 Ad Hoc Committee to Review Publications Program completed, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - A-6-20 Ad Hoc Committee on IRIS, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - A-6-20 Ad Hoc Committee to Study Human Affairs Program (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on New and Experimental Programs, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- ILR Certificates, Dean's Office Plaques (Box 27)